[{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664052214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":17170,"timeElapsed":67189},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664060367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8153,"timeElapsed":75342},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664066458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6089,"timeElapsed":81433},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664069745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3286,"timeElapsed":84720},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664079209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":9463,"timeElapsed":94184},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664082614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3404,"timeElapsed":97589},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664086057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":101032},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664090212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4154,"timeElapsed":105187},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664096812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6599,"timeElapsed":111787},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664109362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11527,"timeElapsed":124337},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664112372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3009,"timeElapsed":127347},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664115652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":130627},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4184,"timeElapsed":134812},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3047,"timeElapsed":137860},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664124417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1531,"timeElapsed":139392},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2291,"timeElapsed":141684},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3888,"timeElapsed":145573},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664132625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":147600},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5952,"timeElapsed":154612},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664143397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":158372},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664158081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14683,"timeElapsed":173056},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664159801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":174776},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2081,"timeElapsed":176857},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664165455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3572,"timeElapsed":180430},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664167551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2095,"timeElapsed":182526},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664171692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4141,"timeElapsed":186667},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1662,"timeElapsed":188330},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664182439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":8457,"timeElapsed":197414},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664183862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1423,"timeElapsed":198837},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664185411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1548,"timeElapsed":200386},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664188328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2916,"timeElapsed":203303},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193913,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5584,"timeElapsed":208888},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":5453,"timeElapsed":214342},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2699,"timeElapsed":217042},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2677,"timeElapsed":219720},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":222598},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2969,"timeElapsed":225568},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664216482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4750,"timeElapsed":231457},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664218577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2095,"timeElapsed":233552},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664221239,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":236214},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":8363,"timeElapsed":244578},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7836,"timeElapsed":252415},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2853,"timeElapsed":255268},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":1562,"timeElapsed":256831},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2652,"timeElapsed":259484},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":261425},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664249156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2705,"timeElapsed":264131},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":35091,"timeElapsed":300030},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2466,"timeElapsed":302497},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664290385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2862,"timeElapsed":305359},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1677,"timeElapsed":307038},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664295429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3366,"timeElapsed":310404},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1725,"timeElapsed":312130},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1714,"timeElapsed":313845},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664300527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1656,"timeElapsed":315501},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":317893},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4152,"timeElapsed":322728},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1639,"timeElapsed":324367},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4084,"timeElapsed":328452},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1749,"timeElapsed":330201},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":332637},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1229,"timeElapsed":333867},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2020,"timeElapsed":335888},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664322885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1971,"timeElapsed":337859},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664324812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1927,"timeElapsed":339787},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6080,"timeElapsed":346648},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":348597},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664337143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3520,"timeElapsed":352118},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1957,"timeElapsed":354076},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2397,"timeElapsed":356474},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664343177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1678,"timeElapsed":358152},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2057,"timeElapsed":360210},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664347851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2616,"timeElapsed":362826},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664349954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":364929},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664355201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4604,"timeElapsed":370176},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664357112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1910,"timeElapsed":372087},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1244,"timeElapsed":373331},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664359943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1586,"timeElapsed":374918},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2885,"timeElapsed":377804},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664363973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1143,"timeElapsed":378948},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4099,"timeElapsed":383048},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2197,"timeElapsed":385246},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664372786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2514,"timeElapsed":387761},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5315,"timeElapsed":394011},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1748,"timeElapsed":395760},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3829,"timeElapsed":399589},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664386185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1569,"timeElapsed":401160},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":403496},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1160,"timeElapsed":404656},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1500,"timeElapsed":406157},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664393036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1853,"timeElapsed":408011},{"subjectID":"j6r25j0shm","prolificID":"660b42d7411787277cf4a709","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216ad96ddca2452a3e5a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1503,"timeElapsed":409514}]